Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology records, 1900-2017
Cornell University, New York State College of Human Ecology records,
- Series II. Dean's Files
  - C. Patsy Brannon (1999-2004)
    - 5. Subject Files
      - Admin-Academic, Strategic Planning, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Admin-College, CALS Dean (Susan Henry), 1995-2005 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Admin-College, Athletic Department, 1995-2003 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Admin-College, Stats, Biostats, Computational Biology, 2001-2003 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Admin-College, Architecture, Art, and Planning, 1995-2004 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Admin-College, Engineering, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Admin-College, Biomedical Engineering, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Admin-College, Leadership Conference, 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Admin-College, Graduate School, 1992-2004 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Admin- College, Industrial Labor Relations, 1994-2004 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Admin- College, Forensics Program, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Admin-College, Veterinary Medicine (New York College of), 1996 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Admin- College, Johnson Grad School of Management, 1994-2000 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Admin-College, Law School (Bill Kell), 1997-2001 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Admin-College, Medical College (Gotto Proposal), 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Admin-College, Medical College, 1999-2004 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Admin-College, Undergraduate Business Program, 2000 Admin-College, Medical College(Weill/Cornell) New York City Initiative, 1998-2004 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Admin College, Arts and Sciences, 1996-2003 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Admin-Colleges, Arts and Sciences, Harry Segal, 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Admin-Committees, Clark Professorship Selection, 1995-2003 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Admin-Committees, Conflict of Interest, 1994-2004 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Admin-Committees, Hatfield Selection Committee, 2000-2004 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Admin-Committees, Memorial Statement Committees (Folder 1), 1994-2003 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Admin- Committees, Memorial Statement Committees, (Folder 2), 1994-2003 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Admin- Committee, Statistic Oversight Committee, Correspondence, Helen Johnson Leipold, 2001-2003 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - Admin-Correspondence, Jean McLean, 2002-2004 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Admin- Correspondence, Morgan, Rebecca, 2002-2003 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Admin- Correspondence, Cindy Noble, 1994-1999 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Admin- Correspondence, Special Friends, 1998-2003 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Admin-Correspondence, Janet Reno, 2003-2004 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Admin- Correspondence, Carol Reich, Beginning with Children, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Admin-Correspondence, University of Helsinki, Wageningen, University, The Netherlands, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Admin- Correspondence, U of Rochester, RWJ Scholars, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Admin-Correspondence, Wells College, 1998-2003 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Admin-Correspondence, Yerka, Bettie Lee, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Admin- Council and Boards, Staff Advisory, Human Ecology, 2000-2004 Admin-Council and Boards, Cornell University Council, 1994-2001 Admin-Council and Boards, International Studies Advisory Council, 2004, 1995-2004 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - Admin- Council and Boards, Staff Advisory, Human Ecology, 2000-2004 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, Cornell University Council, 1994-2001 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, International Studies Advisory Council, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, Professor Emeriti Advisory (Folder 1), 2000-2003 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, Professor Emeriti Advisory (Folder 2), 2000-2003 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, EPE Governing Board (Folder 1), 2000-2004 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, EPE Governing Board (Folder 2), 2000-2004 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, Advisory Council Nominees (Folder 1), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Admin-Council and Boards, Advisory Council Nominees (Folder 2), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Admin-Departments, BLCC Administration-Life Course Center (Folder 1), 1995-2004 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Admin-Departments, BLCC Administration-Life Course Ctr, 1995-2004, 2 BLCC Charter Admin-Departments, BLCC Cornell Gerontology Research Institute, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Admin-Departments, DEA Administration -DEA (Folder 1), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Admin-Departments, DEA Administration -DEA, 1994-2003, 2 Admin-Departments -(DEA)- Non-tenured faculty, 2001-2004, 1994-2004 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Admin-Departments, DEA Administration -DEA, 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Admin-Departments -(DEA)- Non-tenured faculty, 2001-2004 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Admin-Departments- FLDC Administration (Folder 1), 1995-2004 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Admin-Departments- FLDC Administration (Folder 2), 1995-2004 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Admin-Departments, FLDC, CPSTI Office of Children and Family Services (Gladwin and Miraglia OCFS), 1995-2004 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Admin-Departments, FLDC Lawsuit (Westerville), (Folder 1), 1999 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Admin-Departments, FLDC Lawsuit (Westerville), (Folder 2), 1999 (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Admin-Departments, HD Administration, 1996-2004 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Admin-Departments, FLDC Lawsuit (Bruce Chapman), 2004 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Admin-Departments-(DNS) Admin - Div Nutritional Sciences (Folder 1), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - Admin-Departments-(DNS) Admin-Division of Nutritional Sciences (Folder 2), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - Admin-Departments-(DNS) Admin - Div Nutritional Sciences (Folder 3), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Admin-Departments-(DNS) Admin - Div Nutritional Sciences (Folder 4), 1994-2003 (Box 97, Folder 18)
      - Admin-Departments Human Development Social Development Position, 2003-2004 (Box 97, Folder 19)
      - Admin- Departments (HDFS) Early Childhood Center (Folder 1), 1999-2004 (Box 97, Folder 20)
      - Admin- Departments (HDFS) Early Childhood Center, (Folder 2), 1995-2000 (Box 97, Folder 21)
      - Admin- Departments (Human Development), Social Neuroscience Position, 2004-2007 (Box 97, Folder 22)
      - Admin- Deartments (Human Development), Graduate Concentration in Social Science and Law Admin Departments, (Human Development and Family Studies), Early Childhood Center, (Folder noticed missing - October 2016), 2004 (Box 97, Folder 22)
      - Admin- Departments (Human Development and Family Studies) Non-tenured faculty, 1999-2004 (Box 97, Folder 27)
      - Admin-Departments- Division of Nutritional Sceinces, Nutritional Genomics (Mouse Functional Genomics and Human Population Genetics/Genetic Epidemiology,(Folder 1), 2002-2004 (Box 97, Folder 23)
      - Admin-Departments- Division of Nutritional Sciences, Nutritional Genomics (Mouse Functional Genomics and Human Population Genetics/Genetic Epidemiology (Folder 2), 2002-2004 (Box 97, Folder 24)
      - Admin-Departments-(Division of Nutritional Sciences), Non-tenured faculty, 1999-2003 (Box 97, Folder 25)
      - Admin-Departments, Human Metabolic Research Unit, 2000-2004 (Box 97, Folder 25)
      - Admin-Departments, Human Biology, Health and Society, 1998-2001 (Box 97, Folder 25)
      - Admin-Departments (Division of Nutritional Sciences)- Expanded Food and Nutrition Education Program (EFNEP), 1997-2004 (Box 97, Folder 26)
      - Admin-Departments (Division of Nutritional Sciences), Director Search, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Admin-Departments (Division of Nuritional Sciences), Clinical/Metabolic Nutrition, 2000-2004 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Admin-Departments (Division of Nutritional Sciences) Bassett Research Institute and USDA, 2003-2004 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Admin-Departments-(Textiles and Apparel) Non-tenured faculty, 1999-2003 Admin-Departments-(Textiles and Apparel) Administration -Textiles and Apparel, 2000-2004, 1999-2004 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Admin-Departments-(Policy Analysis and Management), Sloan Program/MHA Degree, (Folder 1), 2001-2004 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Admin-Departments-(Policy Analysis and Management), Sloan Program/MHA Degree, (Folder 2), 2001-2004 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Admin-Departments-(Policy Analysis and Management) Non-tenured faculty, 1999-2004 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Admin-Departments-Urban Semester Program, 1997-2004 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Admin-Departments PAM-Consumer/Family/Social Welfare position (Folder 1), 2002-2004 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Admin-Departments Policy Analysis and Management-Consumer/Family/Social Welfare position (Folder 2), 2002-2004 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Admin-Departments Policy Analysis and Management, (Folder 1), 1996-2004 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Admin-Departments Policy Analysis and Management, (Folder 2), 1996-2004 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Admin-Departments Textile and Apparel Program Review, 2003-2004 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Admin-Facilities, MVR Hall, west wing, 2002-2004 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Admin- Facilities, MVR Hall, Student Lounge/Martha's, 2001-2004 (Box 98, Folder 13)
      - Admin- Facilities, MVR Renovation and Rehabilitation, 1933 Building, 1999-2004 (Box 98, Folder 14)
      - Admin- Faculty, Faculty meetings minutes, 2000-2002 (Box 98, Folder 15)
      - Admin- Facilities, MVR Courtyard, 2000-2001 Admin-Facilities, Master Planning Update Committee, 2002-2004, * Master planning files has been removed *, 2000-2004 (Box 98, Folder 16)
      - Admin- Faculty Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - Admin- Faculty Handbook, 1995-2003 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - Admin- Faculty New Research Environment Initiative (Pilot Award Program), 2005 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - Admin- Faculty ,Conversion to nine months, 2002-2004 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      - Admin-Faculty Emeritus Professors, 1992-2004 (Box 98, Folder 18)
      - Admin-Facilities, North-MVR Replacement, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 19)
      - Admin-College Objectives and Priorities, 2003-2004 (Box 98, Folder 20)
      - Admin-Staff, Contract Deans' Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Admin-State, Capital Plan (Folder 1), 2000-2004 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Admin-State, Capital Plan (Folder 2), 2000-2004 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Admin- Policies, Sexual Harassment, 1994-2005 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Admin- Policies, Human Resource Policy, 1995-2003 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Admin- Policies, Faculty/Administration, 1995-2005 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Admin- Organizations, NASULGC Kellogg Commission, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Admin- Organization, NASULGC AAHS/Board of Human Services, 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Admin- Organizations, American Association of Family and Consumer Sciences, 2002-2004 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Admin- Faculty, Recognition of named Professors, 1997-2004 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Admin- Faculty, Three Year Review, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Admin- Faculty, Sabbatical leave/parental leaves, 1994-2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Admin- Faculty, Retirement, 1996-2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Admin- Faculty,Leadership, 2001-2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Admin- Faculty, Kendal at Ithaca Faculty, 2000-2003 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Admin- Faculty, Promotion and Tenure, Titles, 1997-2003 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Admin-Faculty, Gender and Equality Issues, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Admin-Faculty, Faculty Meetings (already bound), 1995-2000 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Admin-Faculty, College Policy on Patent and Royal Income, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Admin- Facilities, North-MVR Replacement,(Folder 1), 2003 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Admin- Facilities, North-MVR Replacement,(Folder 2), 2003 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Admin- State, Land Grant Mission Review, 2002-2003 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - Admin- State, Land Grant and State College Affair Committee, 2001-2004 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Admin- State, SUNY, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - Admin- State, SUNY- "General Supervision" of the New York State Contract Colleges at Cornell, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 31)
      - Admin- State, SUNY- Teacher Education, 1998-2001 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Admin- State, SUNY- State Commissioners- Correspondence, Memos, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Admin- State, SUNY- State Issues Seminars in Albany, 2002-2003 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - Admin-State, State University Construction Fund, 1999-2003 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Admin-State, SUNY Enrollment, 2000-2004 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Admin-State Relations, Govt Offices, Governor's Office, 2000-2004 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Admin-Statistics - Credit Hours and Course Enrollment Reports, 1985-1993; 2004-2005 (Box 105, Folder 31)
      - Admin-Survey - Human Science Survey of Programs and Resources in the College done by Michigan State, 1999 (Box 105, Folder 32)
      - Admin- Task Forces, Athletics, 1998-2003 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Admin- State Tragedy, (September 11, 2001) WTC, Pentagon, War on Iraq, (Folder 1), 2003 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Admin- State Tragedy, (September 11, 2001) WTC, Pentagon, War on Iraq (Folder 2), 2003 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Strategic Planning, 2000-2002 (Box 105, Folder 20-21)
    - 6. Cornell Migrant Program
      - ADMIN-University-President's Council Discussion, 2000 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - ADMIN-Departments-HDFS-Migrant Program, (Folder 1), 1994-2002 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - ADMIN-Departments-HDFS-Migrant Program, (Folder 2), 1994-2002 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - ADMIN-Departments-Human Development and Family Studies-Migrant Program, (Folder 3), 1994-2002 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Notes and Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Press Release, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Review Team, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-State Education Grant, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Transition Team, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Agreed Plan, 2004 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Communication Strategy, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Correspondence from Herb Engman, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Correspondence with Provost, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Correspondence re: CMP, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Internal Review, 2003-06 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - ADMIN-University-Cornell Migrant Program-Internal Review-Responses of Department and CMP Staff (Box 82, Folder 26)
    - 7. Speeches
      - Consumers, Nutrition and Food - What's coming? (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Atlanta Alumni (Human Ecology at Cornell), 2001-11-03 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - CU Staff Orientation Remarks, 2001-11-20 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Time Capsule and Cornerstone of W. Wing, 2001-12-12 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Paul Streeter's Farewell Party Remarks, 2001-12-14 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Commencement Remarks, 2001-12-21 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Retirement Remarks for Carol Anderson (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Kappa Omicron Nu Induction Ceremony, 2001-10-17 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Land Grant and Statutory College Affairs, MVR Emergency, 2001-10-18 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Advancement Committee Facilities Talk, 2001-10-18 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Dean's Lunch, Human Ecology Update, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - At the Heart of the Matter: Translating Research into Meaningful Solutions to Spread the Benefit (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Open House, 2001-10-20 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - CCE New Staff Orientation, 2001-10-24 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Remarks, Iscol Program, 2001-09-25 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Alumni Breakfast, 2001-06-09 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Donor Dinner, 2001-06-06 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Introduction to Joan Jacobs Brumberg, 2001-06-07 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Commencement, 2001-05-27 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - MVR Hall Courtyard Dedication, 2001-05-26 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Merrill Presidential Scholars Convocation, 2001-05-23 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Staff Recognition Awards, 2001-05-03 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Human Ecology Awards Dinner, 2001-04-25 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - New York City Gala, 2001-04-20 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Gathering at Kendal to honor the first Kendal at Ithaca Scholarship started by Roy Unger, 2001-04-18 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Cornell University Women's Club of Syracuse, 2001-04-09 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Human Ecology Centennial Weekend, 2001-04-19 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Centennial Weekend, 2001; CD 3814
      - Core Historical Literature of Home Economics, Advisory Board, 2001-03-26 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - Albany Legislative Briefing-Luncheon, Investing in the Empire State: New York's Children and Youth, 2001-03-06 (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - CCE New Staff Orientation, 2001-02-28 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Investing in the Well-Being of children and Youth (Washington, DC), 2001-02-27 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - "Human Ecology at Cornell University" CHE Ambassadors, 2001-02-12 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - University-wide New Orientation Program for Faculty and Staff, 2001-02-13 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - CU Council Administrative Board (Cornell Club), 2001-02-07 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - "College of Human Ecology" Sarasota Retired Extension, 2001-01-25 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Faculty Mentors Breakfast, 2001-01-31 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - "Human Ecology at Cornell University" Rochester Alumni, 2001-01-13 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Commencement, 2000-12-15 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Cornell-Ithaca Partnership Open House, 2000-12-04 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - College Report, 1999-2000 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - "Nutrition and Women's Health" (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - "Human Ecology at Cornell University" Santa Fe, 2000-11-03 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - Dedication of the Martha Ohaus Bench and Trail, 2000-10-26 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - ACCEE: Connecting at the Crossroads, 2000-10-25 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - The Janet Clay White Lecture in Community Nutrition, 2000-10-20 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Kappa Omicron Nu Induction Ceremony, 2000-10-12 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - "Human Ecology Focus" Cornell Cooperative Extension Orientation, 2000-10-09 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Welcome for Polish Extension Educators, 2000-09-19 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - PCCW Panel Discussion, 2000-09-16 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Emeritus Faculty Event, Cazenovia, New York, 2000-08-24 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Orientation, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Therapeutic Crisis Intervention: An International Perspective, 2000-06-18 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - "College of Human Ecology" Cornell Cooperative Extension New Staff Orientation (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - "Human Ecology at Cornell University" HEAA Reunion Breakfast, 2000 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Donor Dinner, 2000-06-08 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - CCE Extension-Wide Conference, 2000-06-06 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - 4-H Luncheon/Golf Open, 2000-06-02 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Commencement, 2000-5-27 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Merrill Presidential Scholars Convocation, 2000-05-24 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Staff Recognition Award, 2000-05-20 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Statewide Advisory Dinner, Extension-CHE, 2000-05-23 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Second Tuesday, Merrill Ewert, "State of Extension" (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Natalie D. Crowe, Bio for Human Ecology faculty meeting, 2000-04-28 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Human Ecology Awards Dinner, 2000-04-26 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Marion Pfund, Faculty Meeting, 2000-03-14 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - "Human Ecology" Trustees Land Grant and Statutory College Affairs Committee, 2000-03-09 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - Alumni Brunch, Binghamton, 2000-02-26 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "The Current Crisis in Long Term Care" Policy Perspectives Seminar, Albany, New York, 2000-02-08 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - January Commencement Address, 1999-12-17 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "Human Ecology Focus" Rotary Club, 1999-12-15 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "Human Ecology Focus" Alumni Affairs, 1999-12-14 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "Human Ecology Focus" CCE Tompkins County (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "Human Ecology Focus" SUNY Mission Review (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "Human Ecology Focus" Staff Meeting, 1999-11-17 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - Annual NEAFCS-NYA Conference, Compilation of Evaluations, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - "College of Human Ecology" CCE New Staff Orientation (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - "College of Human Ecology" Clarion (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - "Change: Coping, Leading, Enjoying!" Real Estate (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - "College of Human Ecology" NEAFCS (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - "Invest Yourself" Orientation, 1999 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - Welcoming Remarks, 4-H Career Explorations, 1999-06-28 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - EFNEP Conference, 1999-06-15 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - "Leading Change" Donor Dinner (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - "Leading Change" Emeritus Event (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - Speeches, 1999-2001; CD 3811
    - 8. Workforce Planning
      - Workforce Planning - College's Initiative for Finance, 2003-12 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Workforce Planning - Environmental Unit Review, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Workforce Planning - DNS, CALS, HD, 2002-2003 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Workforce Planning - Functional Facilities Review Interviews; External Review Team, 2002-2004 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Workforce Planning - Data Summary, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Workforce Planning - IT Follow-Up, 2004-2006; IT Roles and Responsibilities, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Workforce Planning - IT Recommendations and IT Follow-Up, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Workforce Planning - Informational Technologies, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Workforce Planning - Roles of Deans/Directors; Meeting Agendas, 2002-2005 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Workforce Planning - Human Resources, 2002-2003 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Workforce Planning - Finance, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Workforce Planning - Financial Responsibility Chart (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Workforce Planning - Senior Financial Group Meeting, 2002-2004 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - 9. Chairs and Deans Meetings
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2001-01-2001-06 (Box 75, Folder 27)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2001-03-2001-06 (Box 75, Folder 26)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - D. Lisa Staiano-Coico (2004-2007)
    - 1. Accounting Files
      - ACC Corp Atlantic Philanthropic Service Company, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - ACC Funding and Appropriations, New York State Government Correspondence, Legislators, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - ACC-Accounting and Fiscal Financial Statements, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - ACC-Funding and Appropriations Federal Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - 2. Correspondence